

PHONE 407.283.1401

EMAIL JMAX407@GMAIL.COM

RESPONSIVE DESIGN

WEB JMAXDESIGNS.COM

LOC ORLANDO, FL

Hello my name is Julius, I'm an experienced Front End Developer and Graphic Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the industry. I have strong skills in typography, graphic design, web design, UI / UX, and creating responsive designs that work on multiple devices. Please visit my online portfolio, www.jmaxdesigns.com for work examples.

EXPERIENCE

US DOD COINS

JAN 2016 - MAY 2018

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPMENT

Redesign of company website, creation on digital marketing campaigns for facebook and instagram, email campaigns, and product design for clients.

MARRIOTT VACATION CLUB

MAY 2014 - NOV 2015

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPMENT

Responsible for design of the internal User interface of Marriott Vacation Club System within the Marriott Brand standard. Design and develop web pages from initial Photoshop comps to prototype and live production using HTML, CSS and Javascript.

XULON PRESS

MAY 2013 - MARCH 2014

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPMENT

UI Design and frontend development of internal book buying admin system. Responsible for providing backend developers with HTML and CSS.

SOFTROCK INC

SEPT 2010 - MAY 2013

GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER

Design of various graphics on various media outlets (flyer, tv, desktop) used in and out of office. Design and develop from initial Photoshop comps to production using HTML and CSS.

ORLANDO MAGAZINE

2009-2010

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

Work with art director and lead designer to create compelling graphic and advertising for print magazine. Also assist staff photographer on photoshoots.

EDUCATION

VALENCIA COLLEGE

2008 - 2010

DEGREES

AS Degree in Graphic Technology with a specialization in Print Technology AS Degree in Graphic Technology with a specialization in Web Technology

SKILLSFT

HTML	BOOTSTRAP	WORDPRESS
РНОТОЅНОР	css	DIGITAL PHOTOGRAPHY
INDESIGN	ILLUSTRATOR	JQUERY